bailbondcity.com 2017-02-19

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Effective Date: 1/19/2017

Bail Bond City (“we” or “us”) collects certain information about you through BailBondCity.com (our “Website” or “Site”) and our Bail Bond City mobile app (our “App”). We care about your privacy and this page lays out our policies and procedures surrounding the collection and handling of any information we collect from you. The Website and the App may be collectively referred to as the “Software.”

Your use of our Website and download and use of our App constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy and forms a legally-binding contract between you and us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, immediately discontinue use of our Software and delete our App from your mobile device.

This Privacy Policy applies only to our Software. It does not apply to any information that is not collected via our Software.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect two different kinds of information from you:

  * Personally Identifiable Information (or “PII”) is information that could be used to identify you as an individual or that could be used to contact or locate you.
  * Non-Personally Identifiable Information (or “non-PII”) is any other kind of information we collect from you.

**How and when do we collect your information?**

We collect your information both actively and passively.  Active data collection occurs when you enter your information into a form on our Software. Passive data collection occurs without your affirmative consent by our Software’s use of browser cookies and other analytic and reporting technologies.  Browser cookies are small files usually used to persist data between browser sessions by saving certain pieces of non-PII. It allows the browser to “remember” what you did the last time you visited our Site or used our App.

You may also visit our Site or use our App anonymously—that is, without explicitly entering your information into our Software. If you visit our Site or use our App anonymously, we will not perform active data collection but we will still perform passive data collection.

__Actively collected PII__ _:_ We collect your email address, your name, your phone number, and your address when you enter it on our Software. These data items are considered PII because each of them can be used individually to identify you or to contact you. We also collect any PII you enter as a message or upload onto our “Contact Us” form.

__Actively collected non-PII:__ We also collect any non-PII you enter as a message or upload onto our “Contact Us” form.

__Passively collected PII__ _:_ We will never collect PII from you without your affirmative consent.

__Passively collected non-PII__ _:_ We collect certain anonymous information about your use of our Software. Examples of this anonymous information are: your browser type, your device’s operating system, the date and time of your access to our website, geographical information, browser history, and device type. This is not an exhaustive list of the types of passive non-PII we may collect; it merely provides examples of the kinds of data we may collect.

**What do we use your information for?**

The PII we collect from you may be used to communicate with you. We may also sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your PII to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses so we can keep our free offerings free.

The non-PII we collect from you may be used in any of the following ways:

  * To improve our Software (we continually strive to improve our Software offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To comply with applicable legal requirements or industry standards.

**How do we protect your information?**

We use malware scanning to safeguard your information against legal intrusion and unauthorized access. No security measures are 100% reliable, however, so we cannot warranty the security of your PII.

**__You understand and agree that you are using our Software at your own risk. You assume all responsibility and risk for use of our Software.__**

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

Yes, we may sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your PII and non-PII to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses so we can keep our free offerings free.

We may also disclose your PII to trusted third-party service providers who assist us in operating our Software, conducting our business, or servicing you. These trusted service providers are not allowed to use your PII for any purposes other than those to which they have been entrusted. We shall use reasonable efforts to ensure these service providers hold your PII in confidence and we shall only disclose your PII to third parties that we believe in good faith practice acceptable privacy and security measures.

We may also release your information when we believe its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or other’s rights, property, or safety.

In addition, we may transfer your PII as part of a sale, merger, acquisition, or other change of control. We may also transfer your PII to protect our legal rights in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, reorganization, receivership, assignment, or any application of creditor’s rights.

**Where do we store your information?**

We store your information in servers owned by a reputable cloud provider. Your use of our Software acts as your consent to transfer your PII outside of you country of residence if such servers reside outside of your country of residence.

**What about third-party links on the Website or accessible from the App?**

We may have links to third-party websites on our Website and accessible from our App. These third parties are provided to give you access to other resources, products, and services. **__Once you click on a third party’s link that is accessible from our Software, your information (both PII and non-PII) is covered under the privacy policy of that third party and is no longer under our control.__**

**What is our policy with regard to children?**

We will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of thirteen (13) as is consistent with COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). In the unlikely event you discover your child under the age of thirteen has supplied us with PII, you may contact us using the information provided in this Privacy Policy and we will remove your child’s information from our database.

**Can we modify this Privacy Policy?**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice to you, by posting a new version on this page or on a successor page. The new version will become effective on the date it is posted, which will be listed at the top of the page as the new effective date. Your continued use of our Software is your acceptance of the new terms of the Privacy Policy.

**How can you contact us?**

If there are questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us using the information below:

Bail Bond City

7643 Gate Parkway

Suite 104-559

Jacksonville, Florida 32256

info@bailbondcity.com
